5... 4... 3...
5...4...3...
Sun Yu Chang is a member of the trade delegation now in Boston.
Sun Yu Chang是贸易代表团的一名成员  现在在波士顿.
They've been talking to our governor.
他们在和我们州长进行会谈.
How are the talks going, Mr. Chang?
会谈进展怎么样, Mr.Chang?
Very, very well.
非常非常好.
Can you tell us how well?
你能告诉我们有多好吗?
It's a negotiation.
它是一个谈判.
We don't agree on every point.
我们并不是每一个观点都一致.
And we are dealing with issues that affect trade everywhere.
并且我们正在处理的问题 会影响各个地方的贸易.
For instance?
例如?
Inflation, of course.
通货膨胀, 当然.
Here, compared with inflation in our country.
这里, 和我们国家的通货膨胀相比.
Also employment.
还有 就业问题.
How much of our workforce is involved in trade with your country.
有多少我们的劳动力参与到同你们国家的贸易中.
These affect our discussions.
这些影响我们的讨论.
Will there be a trade agreement?
将会形成一个贸易协议吗?
Oh yes. We are making progress all the time.
Oh yes. 我们一直在取得进展.
Thank you for speaking with us, Mr. Chang.
谢谢你和我们谈话, Mr.Chang.
My pleasure.
我的荣幸.
Sun Yu Chang, ending on a positive note.
Sun Yu Chang, 结束在一个积极的音符上.
This is Heather Vialo reporting live from the Sheraton Boston,
这里是Heather Vialo现场直播  来自Sheraton Boston
for the Business Network.
为商业网络.
OK. We're all set.
OK. 我们完成了.
Thank you , Mr. Chang.
谢谢你, Mr.Chang.